

Bruce Page

17830 Virginia Avenue Hagerstown, MD 21740 (301) 730.9365 rbrucepage@yahoo.com

SUMMARY:

UX expert and front end developer with 13+ years building E-commerce and promotional marketing collateral. Recognizing, managing, and cultivating young stars into superstars. Growing online businesses through creative thinking, strategic planning and execution, strong, relevant and non-intrusive user experiences, and close partnerships with key business and team leaders. Proven track record of managing many successful website launches that have resulted in millions in online business growth.

EDUCATION:

John Herron School of Art and Design, Indiana University | 1997 – 2000

BFA - Visual Communication

WORK HISTORY:

The Big Idea Supply Company :: Hagerstown, MD | 2/08 - current

Creative Director, Principal

- Develop creative solutions every day that compel user engagement on the Internet.
- Work with clients to develop concepts and strategies that leverage best-in-class tools and best practices in device-driven communication.
- Provide consultation to those needing some help getting their visual communication collateral to the next level.
- Help define and strengthen the perception of a product and/or brand's identity online.
- Develop engaging sales creative that communicate all of the essentials, but gets out of the way and encourages the user to take action.



Bruce Page

17830 Virginia Avenue Hagerstown, MD 21740 (301) 730.9365 rbrucepage@yahoo.com

Healthy Directions, LLC :: Potomac, MD | 4/04 - current

Executive Director, Web Design

- Oversee all aspects of the Internet marketing internal creative agency.
 Lead a design team, which produces 200 outgoing online direct-to-consumer marketing efforts per month.
- Collaborate with internal and external stakeholders to develop best-in-class online collateral including: E-commerce and promotional websites, E-newsletters, landing pages, rich media banner placement, broadcast emails, Social marketing efforts and online streaming media through all possible Internet communication channels including PPC campaigns and affiliate relationships.
- Ensure implementations are timely and effective per brand guidelines, statistical analysis and user experience best practices.
- Implement state-of-the art content management tools + work with ECP vendors to ensure smooth platform migrations. Create specs and test plans to verify platform performance and stability in staging environments prior to roll out.
- Partner with other business leaders to brainstorm, develop, and execute annual online business strategies.
- QA websites to verify coding best practices are being applied and maintained in all online creative to facilitate SEO optimization, accessibility standards compliance and full browser support in all desktop and mobile environments. Provide recommendations and manage updates if modifications are required.
- Oversee development of SOPs to maintain transparent communication of current processes and provide reference materials to new employees.
- Create cohesive team environment and facilitate continued growth through regular internal training sessions, 1:1 weeklies with individual team members, benchmarking exercises and critiquing, off-site courses and conferences, and goal setting with regular progress check-ins.
- Provide creative consultation to Executive management as it pertains to ways we might leverage the Internet to expand business opportunities. Recommendations are regularly implemented and successful.



Bruce Page

17830 Virginia Avenue Hagerstown, MD 21740 (301) 730.9365 rbrucepage@yahoo.com

Kaplan University :: Hagerstown, MD | 7/02 - 4/04

Full-Time Instructor

- Instructed a variety of classes on software packages including Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and Flash.
- Instructed several courses on principals of graphic design, digital video production and color theory.
- Responsible for recommending software, installing and maintaining on 45+ Apple computers and file servers across the college's internal network.
 Enhanced management skills through regular team building exercises and inherent student management responsibilities.
- Was recognized by the college as the preferred instructor in the Graphics department based on end-of-semester student evaluation feedback for 3 consecutive semesters.

Ellipsis Design :: Hagerstown, MD | 12/02 - 4/04

Creative Director | Partner

- Responsible for all creative executions presented to clients. Managed junior designer.
- Specked out projects and provided LOE assessments and quotes based on project requirements.
- Managed, built and retained relationships working 1:1 with clients.
- Worked with external vendors to deliver print and online-based collateral in various formats, always on time and within budget.
- Active member of the deign community. Joined AIGA and participated in numerous events.
- Managed all aspects of the business, including: taxes, payroll, legal and accounting consultation, business marketing and networking, Business incorporation.
- Aimed to exceed client expectations. Regularly received accolades from customers.
 Me being easy to work with was a regular complement, and reason why I was requested on projects often.



Bruce Page

17830 Virginia Avenue Hagerstown, MD 21740 (301) 730.9365 rbrucepage@yahoo.com

mediumFUSION, LLC Graphic Arts Group :: Indianapolis, IN | 2/01 - 5/02

Creative Director | Partner

- Responsible for creative executions presented to clients.
- Specked out projects and provided LOE assessments and quotes based on project requirements.
- Managed, built and retained relationships working 1:1 with clients.
- Worked with external vendors to deliver print and online-based collateral in various formats, always on time and within budget.
- Aimed to exceed client expectations. Regularly received accolades from customers. Me being easy to work with was a regular complement, and reason why I was requested on projects often.

Career Note: Additional experience: Adjunct Professor, John Herron School of Art | Indianapolis, IN: Fall 1998, 2001 – 2002 • Art Director, Robert Feldman and Associates | Bethesda, MD: 2000 – 2001

Intrnships: Indiana Pacers | Conseco Fieldhouse: Interior and Display Design | designer, 1998–1999 Iris Centre for Digital Arts: Advertising and Marketing | designer, 1999